Preston Casey Palmer

User Experience Designer

Dedicated to developing digital products with cutting edge design and graceful degradation. Strengths in creativity, teamwork, and building projects from ideation to execution. Fine arts background coupled with strong research skills and an eye for modern design principles, makes me a valuable addition to any team.

Contact

https://uxfol.io/86afd34d preston.c.palmer@gmail.com 612-229-6853

Education

UXUI Bootcamp - 2022University of Minnesota

B.A. in Sociology - 2014University of Minnesota

Skills

User Experience
Content Management
Information Architecture
Copy Writing & Editing
User Research
Prototyping
Design Systems
Front-End Development
Wordpress Administration
Project Management

Projects

UX Design Project | Collectively App

The aim of this project was to design a fully functional app design that would help people in their everyday lives.

Skills | Technologies Used: Stakeholder Interviews, User Research (Interviews + Surveys)
 & Analysis, Persona Creation, User Experience Design (UI/UX), Interaction Design,
 Prototyping, In-Person User Testing, Figma & FigJam, and InVision

Experience

Self-Employed

2018 - present

Multimedia Artist

- Design, implement, and maintain a fully functional WordPress website using the GoDaddy hosting platform.
- Create unique images, video, and audio to accompany dynamic web-based written content.

Värde Partners

2019 - 2021

RFP Analyst

- Oversee the completion of investor and prospect reporting requests including RFPs,
 DDQs and document requests
- Oversee Word and PowerPoint content creation, routine updates, and management in Upland Qvidian proposal automation software

Voya Financial

2016 - 2018

Administrative Assistant

- Provided support to 5 managers and back-up support for senior leaders as needed
- Ran daily, weekly, and monthly reports, scheduled meetings
- Formatted, edited and proofread Word documents, emails, and senior-level PowerPoint Presentations
- Planned and executed events for over 500 people

Interactive Design Inc.

2008 - 2016

Web-Development Assistant

- Copy-writing and copy-editing for client web-pages
- Data-entry and PHP/MySQL database management
- Professional image editing in Adobe Photoshop
- Coding HTML, CSS, and PHP in Adobe Dreamweaver